That-That's okay.
I can infer from context.
Hey, Raj, you wanna see a new
magic trick I been working on?
Eh, Howard.
(Sheldon:)If I may interject here
with a piece of friendly advice.
(Sheldon:)Is working on magic tricks, really
how you want to spend your time?
Uh, granted,
you're just an engineer, but...
(Sheldon:)That doesn't mean you might
not someday build a geegaw
(Sheldon:)or a thingamabob that
that may get you a "thank you" in someone
else's Nobel Prize acceptance speech.
(Raj:)Is the trick making him disappear?
(Raj:)Sure, let's see it.
(Sheldon:)Here.
Shuffle these.
(Priya:)Okay.
(Howard:)Now spread them out on the table.
Face down.
(Howard:)Pick one.
Look at it.
(Priya:)Okay.
(Howard:)Now remember your card.
Put it back in the deck.
(Sheldon:)Is it any wonder
he doesn't have a doctorate?
Now remind me,
what's your birthday?
(Raj:)October sixth.
(Howard:)Okay, October is the tenth month.
So 10-- one plus zero
is one plus six is seven.
(Howard:)Turn over the seventh card.
(Raj:)How about that!
But, is that your card?
(Raj:)Yes. It is.
Very cool!
Oh it's not cool.
(Sheldon:)It's a childish trick, designed
to confuse and intrigue simpletons.
(Sheldon:)How'd you do it?
(Howard:)A magician never reveals his secrets.
(Howard:)But surely a future
Nobel Prize winner can figure it out.
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)Give me a second.
(Howard:)You ever notice when he thinks
real hard it smells like bacon?
- Oh hey!
- Sorry! Oop!
(Leonard:)Check it out.
I just got contacts.